mortystv.com 2002-12-09

# Ask Morty Legal & Privacy Information

Privacy Statement for Ask Morty

**Privacy & Legal Statements for Morty's TV:**

Morty has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: MortysTV.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. We may use cookies to determine what pages are popular and get repeat views.  All information collected on Morty's TV,  pertains to our web site,  and not our visitors.

This site contains links to other sites. Morty's TV is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Some content on this site is provided by third party affiliations.  By accessing their content, it is possible for these sites to send cookies and collect the IP addresses of our visitors.  Some of these providers include, but are not limited to:  Isyndicate.com, Zap2It, NewsHub, ABC News and Yahoo.com.  The amount of information, if any,  these sites can collect is limited,  however you should contact these providers for their privacy statements if you have concerns.

Morty's TV  does not share information with any outside parties. We do not share or sell your email address or other information.

Any online surveys or email form that may ask you for contact information (like your email address) it is used to contact you only when necessary.   If we run contests on our site in which we ask for contact information (like  email addresses),  the contact information is used to contact you for winner notification.  The Trivia Blitz game is owned and produced by Uproar Entertainment.  Praedo Systems and www.MortysTV.com  accept no responsibility for the delivery of prizes.  Uproar Entertainment collects personal information including email addresses.  This information is not shared with www.MortysTV.com, and you should contact Uproar Entertainment to determine how their information is used. 

MortysTV.com may, at times sell advertising space to companies that use banner ads to place cookies on your computer that can be used to gather internet marketing information.  We understand that some people my find this practice offensive.  Information received with banner ad cookies is collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. For visitors that would like more information on protecting their privacy,  we suggest you visit the [Junk Buster](http://www.junkbuster.com/) web site. For more information about cookies, visit [Cookie Central](http://www.cookiecentral.com/bug/index.shtml).  If you choose to turn off cookies while using our site, everything should continue to function, however affiliates such as amazon.com require cookies enabled to use their shopping carts.  To view our banner ad affiliate's privacy policy, [Click Here](http://www.cj.com/privacy.asp).

**Content:**  
Our content is not rated. Because of the nature of the entertainment industry, and a desire to present un-censored quotes, we have found it too restrictive to limit our content to a particular ratings level.   In general,  sexual content is limited to clinical terms,  there are few, if any,  nude photographs, and no sexually explicit images.  Violent content is limited to the type they may be seen in an "R" rated movie, and the objectionable language used on this site will rarely exceed  "common slang."  

Although not credited, some content is provided by outside contributors.  As with all content on Morty's TV, there is no guarantee of the information's accuracy.    

Our site contain thousands of links to outside web sites.  Morty's TV  does not control the content of these sites.  We assume no responsibility for the content of these sites.  If you believe a link on our web site is offensive, and may have been included in error,  please notify us by sending us feedback.

This service is provided for the information of users only. It is not provided with the  intention that users rely upon the information for any purposes. Accordingly, Morty's TV  shall under no circumstances be liable for any loss or damage, including but not limited to loss of profits, goodwill or indirect or consequential loss arising out of any use of or inaccuracies in the information contained on this web site. All warranties express or implied are excluded to the fullest extent permissible by law.

All information in this site is © 1999-2002. Praedo Systems.  Reproduction, distribution or transmission by any means without the prior permission of Praedo Systems is prohibited. All rights reserved.  Would you like to use some Morty in your print or internet publication?  Click Here. 

Some images use on this site are used under license granted by Media Graphics Inc.  and are Copyright © by Media Graphics Inc., 1998.   All trademarks are property of their legal owners.  Many of the celebrity images were provided to the site author for press/promotional purposes at the time of release of the property being promoted.  As these images/likenesses and logos are the remain property of the studios and stars that issued the original images, these owners have the right to determined how they are used.   If you believe Morty has illegally used artwork/images/photos that you are the rightful owner thereof, please contact Praedo Systems by mail at:  Post Office Box, Medford, NJ USA 08055, by fax at: (609) 953-0769, or by email at: [legal@mortystv.com](mailto:legal@mortystv.com)

www.MortysTV.com  is not affiliated nor endorsed by any of the shows or networks featured on this site.  All network and show names are trademarks or property of their copyright owners and are used in recognition of their owners. This is not an official site of any network or show. All logos, images, and sounds are copyrighted to their respective owners.  The _"Big Brother"_ pages on this site  have no affiliation with Big Brother, Our House Productions Inc., Endemol Entertainment USA, Inc., CBS Broadcasting, Viacom or any of it's parent companies or entities.  Additional information about "Big Brother" coverage is available in a separate FAQ file found here.

**Submissions and Contributions:  
**MortysTV.com does not accept submissions for conventional royalty publishing,  no financial considerations or payments will be paid for any content used by Morty.  Unsolicited manuscripts can not be returned without return postage paid.   As you read this statement, you may be asking "why would anyone want to write without compensation?"  Ask Morty operates on the same principle as Public Television:  If you enjoy it, you might want to donate something to help keep it going.   Television and network publicists who wish to send press releases should read these instructions. 

**Additional Cautions:  
**This website is best viewed on a computer.  www.MortysTV.com is intended for external use only. Do not attempt to drive or operate a heavy machinery while using this website. Take only as directed.  If symptoms persist, consult your physician.  No user serviceable parts inside. Do not use near fire or flame. Do not exceed recommended dosage. Do not use in or near water.  Caution: Filling is hot.   

**A Little Credit:  
**Some of the HTML templates used on this site were designed by [Knight Networking and Web Design](http://www.knightnetworking.com/).  Custom graphics, Flash and Shockwave animations by Praedo Systems.  Stock graphics and sounds by Media Graphics Inc..  Some schedule information and research provided by Paven Patel of [Jack's Bistro](http://www.jacksbistro.freeservers.com/).  The Morty TV News Java Ticker and some CGI scripts were designed by J. Michael Smith Custom Programming.  To  license the news applet for other purposes, contact: [legal@mortystv.com](mailto:legal@mortystv.com)  The custom programming that makes our news pages so great were written by Casey Jones of [Tryph.com](http://tryph.com/).  

**Contacting the Web Site:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  [legal@mortystv.com](mailto:legal@mortystv.com)

To contact us by mail:  
Morty's TV  
c/o Praedo Systems  
Post Office Box 272  
Medford, NJ USA  08055 

Fax: 609-953-0769 

The information and policies stated on this page is subject to change without notice. 

Last Updated:  Sunday, November 10, 2002
